gmfinancial.com 2019-05-18

# Privacy Statement | GM Financial

## Online Privacy Policy

GM Financial is committed to respecting and protecting customer privacy. The Online Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”) explains what information GM Financial may collect about you when you use the GM Financial website, [https://www.gmfinancial.com](https://www.gmfinancial.com/), or mobile application (collectively, “Site”) or the products or services offered through the Site (“Services”) and how we use and protect that information. Please read the Privacy Policy carefully. By using the Site or the Services, you consent to the collection and use of your personal information as described in the Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with the terms of the Privacy Policy, please do not use the Site or Services.

The Site is controlled, operated, and administered by GM Financial from its offices within the United States. If you are accessing the Site from a location outside the United States, you acknowledge and consent to the collection, storage, processing, and transfer of your personal information to our facilities in the United States and to those third-parties with whom we share it as described in this Statement.

### Table of Contents

  * Collecting Personal Information
  * Using Personal Information
  * Third-Party Collection of Personal Information
  * Disclosing Personal Information to Third-Parties
  * Making Changes to Your Information
  * Do Not Track
  * Security
  * Mobile Application
  * Children’s Privacy
  * Changes to the Privacy Policy
  * Effective Date

### Collecting Personal Information

GM Financial may collect, store, and use the following kinds of personal information:

  * Information you provide to us when you register on MyAccount, including your first and last names, GM Financial account number, Social Security number, e-mail address, and vehicle information such as make, model, and vehicle identification number ("VIN");

  * Information you provide when completing an online GM Financial credit application, including your first and last names, physical address, residence type, length of time at current address, monthly rent or mortgage amount, home and business telephone numbers, e-mail address, date of birth, Social Security number, employment status, job title, employer name, employer phone number, length of time at place of employment, and income information;

  * Information from commercially available third-party sources, such as consumer reporting agencies and identity verification services, which may be combined with the information you provide when completing an online GM Financial credit application;

  * Information about the device or computer you use to access the Site, including device ID, device and platform type, operating system, IP address, browser type and version, domain name, and referring website/service/application; and 

  * Information that you send directly to GM Financial or post to any of GM Financial’s social media websites for publication on the Internet, such as your first and last names, user name, profile picture, user preferences such as “Like” button clicks, and the content of your posts.

### Using Personal Information 

We may use personal information that we collect in the following ways:

  * To provide you with Services and to fulfill our contractual obligations to you;
  * To process your GM Financial online credit application;
  * To communicate with you about the Site or Services, such as to send you account updates or other communications regarding your account or to inform you of any changes to the Site or Services;
  * To send you information about promotions or other marketing material;
  * For specific purposes for which you provide consent;
  * To provide you support or other services you request, for example technical support or to answer questions about the Site;
  * To maintain and improve the Site and Services and improve user experience; and
  * For any other legitimate business purpose.

### Third-Party Collection of Personal Information

GM Financial may allow third-party service providers to place persistent identifiers such as cookies, pixel tags, and web beacons on the Site.

Cookies, pixel tags, and web beacons are used for the following purposes:

  * Analytical Purposes: We use cookies and web beacons to analyze user activity in order to improve the Site. For example, we use this information to determine the number of visitors to the Site, the pages viewed per visit, and the time spent on particular pages. Collecting this information helps us provide you with a better online experience.

  * User Preferences: We may use cookies, pixel tags, and web beacons to store preferences you demonstrate on the Site. For instance, we may use a cookie to store your User ID so that you do not need to re-enter it every time you visit MyAccount.

  * Marketing: We may use cookies and web beacons from third-party service providers for marketing purposes to place GM Financial advertisements on non-affiliated websites. We may also use service providers who use tracking devices such as cookies, pixel tags, and web beacons to collect anonymized information about consumers’ activities on non-affiliated websites. The information they collect typically includes things like browser type, IP address, pages visited, and time visited. GM Financial may use this information to provide relevant marketing content to you. You may opt out of receiving such advertisements on the advertisement itself. You may be able to opt out of some third party service providers’ use of cookies by visiting the [Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp) or the [Digital Advertising Alliance’s Opt-Out page](http://optout.aboutads.info/). 

One of the third-party services that we use is Google Analytics, which is a web analysis service provided by Google. Google utilizes the data collected to track and examine the use of the Site and may share this data with other Google services. We also use the Google AdWords remarketing service to advertise on third-party websites. Google may show GM Financial advertisements on websites across the Internet and may use cookies to serve advertisements based on your past visits to the Site. You can find information about how to opt out of Google's use of cookies by visiting [Google's Ads Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/ads).

The Site may also include social media features, such as the Facebook “Like” button, and other widgets, such as the “Share” button or interactive mini-programs provided by third-parties. These third-parties may use cookies or other tracking technologies to collect information about you when you use the Site. The information they collect may be associated with your personal information or they may collect information, including personal information, about your online activities over time and across different websites and other online services. 

### Disclosing Personal Information to Third-Parties

We may disclose personal information we collect from you to the following third-parties, for the purposes specified:

  * Service Providers. We may use third-parties to provide you with products and services you request. If you are a customer, we may disclose the information we collect about you as described herein and in accordance with GM Financial customer privacy notices and applicable law.
  * Affiliates. For customers, we may share personal information within the General Motors family of companies for analytical purposes, user preferences, and marketing in accordance with GM Financial’s customer privacy notices and applicable law. 
  * Dealers. We may share your credit application information with the dealer you select during the credit application process, in accordance with the terms and conditions of that process and applicable law. 
  * Change in Corporate Structure: We may share information in connection with a merger, acquisition, consolidation, change of control, or sale of all or a portion of our assets or if we undergo bankruptcy or liquidation.
  * Consumer Reporting Agencies: We may report the status of your account with us to consumer reporting agencies. 
  * Other Disclosures. We may also disclose your personal information when we are required to do so by law; with your consent; or when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process.

### Making Changes to Your Information

You may make changes to the information that you provide to us on the MyAccount Site by logging into MyAccount and selecting “My Profile.” You may also select the “Contact Us” tab on the Site to ask us any questions. 

### Do Not Track 

Certain web browsers may provide an option by which you can have the browser inform websites, or Internet services you visit that you do not wish to have your activities tracked by cookies or other persistent identifiers across time and across third-party Internet websites, online or cloud computing services, online applications, or mobile applications. These are commonly called "Do Not Track" signals. At this time, the Site does not honor Do Not Track signals from web browsers because it may diminish the optimal performance of the Site. However, you may refuse or delete cookies. Please refer to your browser’s Help instructions to learn more about cookies and other technologies, and how to manage their use. If you do elect to refuse or delete cookies, you will need to repeat this process if you use another computer or change browsers. If you choose to decline cookies, some of the functionalities of websites may be impaired.

### Security

We maintain reasonable physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards designed to protect against loss or unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction of the information you provide on the Site. However, no method of transmission over the Internet or electronic storage technology is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. The security of your information also depends on the security of the electronic devices and Internet Service Provider network that you use to access the Site. We are not responsible for the security of your information accessed on those devices or networks.

### Mobile Application

We may offer you the ability to access your GM Financial account on your mobile devices via the GM Financial My Account Mobile Application (“My Account App”). When you use the My Account App, we may collect information described in the section above, titled Collecting Personal Information. We may also collect information about your mobile device, device settings, screen resolution, information about your location, and analytical information about how you use your mobile device. Some mobile devices may allow you to limit the sharing of personal information collected by applications that run on those devices, or information collected by the devices themselves. We may ask permission before collecting certain information (such as precise geo-location information) through the My Account App.

For your convenience, you may be able to use biometric authentication (using Touch ID, Fingerprint, or Face ID) provided through your mobile device manufacturer to access your GM Financial account. (Please refer to your mobile device manufacturer’s product information for details on biometric functionality for your device.) To enable biometric authentication for logging into the My Account App, you are required to save your GM Financial user name and password on your device. GM Financial does not control the fingerprint, Touch ID or Face ID functionality. GM Financial does not have access to your fingerprint(s) or facial recognition information. You understand and agree that any fingerprint or facial recognition information stored on this device can be used to access your GM Financial customer account information. We recommend that you employ a strong device password as an additional layer of security. 

### Children’s Privacy

The Site is not intended for use by children under the age of 13 years, and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13 years. Please contact us if you believe we may have unknowingly collected information about a child under 13, and we will take immediate steps to delete any such personal information.

### Changes to the Privacy Policy

We may modify this Privacy Policy at any time. If we do, we will post the revised version on this page. You should periodically check here for the most up-to-date version of this Privacy Policy. Any changes to the Privacy Policy will not be retroactively applied and will not alter how we handle any personal information we previously collected from you.

### Effective Date

This Privacy Policy is effective as of April 12, 2018.
